你怎么不說話 生我氣了嗎
Why aren't you talking, are you mad at me?
不 我是被發現自己懷孕這件事嚇到了
No! I'm freaked because I just found out that I'm pregnant.
不過我確實有點生你的氣
And yes, I am a little mad at you,
因為這事很嚴肅
because this is serious,
但你唯一能想到的卻是
and the only thing that you can think about
把我們的名字組合成完美的寶寶名字
is combining our names into the perfect baby name.
至少現在知道寶寶不是叫海登就是叫迪莉
Well, now we know it's either Hayden or Dyley.
這是件美好的事情
Look, this is a beautiful thing.
我們愛的結晶
A product of our love.
是"我們"的愛的結晶吧
It is a product of our love, right?
是的 迪蘭 我算過了
Yes, Dylan. I did the math.
上次你算數的時候
Last time you did the math
我們不小心留下了300美元的小費
we accidentally left a $300 tip.
我不知道該怎么辦
Oh, I don't know what to do.
這樣如何
How about this?
海莉·格溫多林·鄧菲
Haley Gwendolyn Dunphy...
你愿意嫁給我嗎
will you marry me?
你現在是在開玩笑嗎
Are you kidding me right now?
想象一下我們一起走過紅毯的畫面
Picture us walking down the aisle,
一位妙人身穿著純白無暇的禮服
a breathtaking vision in virginal white
而你穿著自己想穿的衣服
and you wearing whatever you want.
我不要嫁給你
I'm not marrying you!
好吧 好吧 我們慢慢來
Okay, okay, one step at a time.
我們先給你補充維生素 打造健康飲食
We'll put you on vitamins and a healthy diet.
你現在是一人吃給寶寶補了
You'll be eating for one now.
好極了 是棒棒糖
Score! Lollipops!
我該怎么和我媽媽說
How am I gonna tell my mom?
她一直不讓我做的就是這件事
This is the one thing she always told me not to do,
而你就是那個她說不要一起做的人
and you're the person she told me not to do it with.
是啊 她說得真是準
Yeah, she really nailed that one.
希望咱們的寶寶能有她的聰明才智
I hope our baby gets her brain.
你為什么一點都不害怕
Why aren't you freaking out?
因為這是好事啊
Because this is a good thing,
難道不是嗎
isn't it?
我...
I...
我不知道
I don't know.
天哪 我得去上班了
Oh, my God, I have to get to work.
我喜歡那工作 但我甚至都不知道
To a job that I love, which I don't even know
它允不允許帶孕上班
if I can do with a baby!
只是 我
Just -- I, um...
我需要點空間
I need some space.
13美元 3進位...
$13, carry the 3...
留50美元小費吧
Leave a $50.
很好 湯普森
All right, Thompson,
干凈利落點 平托斯基 沖啊
run a crisp route! Pitkowski, go!
看看這群人
Look at them out there.
他們一團糟 注意力不集中
They are a mess. No focus!
你告訴過他們不要吃雞肉了 對吧
You told them about not eating chicken, right?
那小鳥容易緊張不安
It's a nervous bird.
比賽之前 應該吃點平和的哺乳動物
Before the game, you eat your calm mammals,
牛肉啊 羊肉啊之類的
your beefs, your muttons.
好了 大家過來這邊
Okay, guys, get in here!
我們走 集中起來
Let's go. Huddle up!
我們即將參加城市冠軍賽
We're about to play for the city championship,
杰一直在幫忙
and Jay here has been helping out.
我當團隊鼓舞員的角色有很多年了
I've been a team booster for years.
一般來說這意味著
Usually that means cutting a check
由普里契特關懷基金開張支票
from the Pritchett Cares Foundation.
我們支持運動員
We support athletics
以及對問題少年們進行衣柜職業教育
and we educate at-risk youth about careers in closets.
這是一條真正的出路
It's a real path out.
好了 今天是你們生命中最重要的一天
Okay, this is the biggest day of your lives
但你們看起來就像是一群小女孩
and you're looking like a bunch of little girls out there!
怎么 平托斯基 芭比娃娃忘帶了嗎
What's wrong, Pitkowski, did you forget your Barbies?!
教練 我們一直在討論
Coach, we've been talking,
你最近說的話
and the language you've been using lately
感覺很傷人
feels, well, hurtful.
還有些性別歧視
And sexist.
還有一點性別簡化
And a little gender reductive.
這究竟是怎么回事
What the hell is happening?
我們只是希望你能
We'd just like you to consider
考慮一下用鼓勵代替辱罵的方式
adopting a more empowering style.
你知道嗎
Okay, you know what?
這是橄欖球
This is football!
怎么 你們的訓練胸罩太緊了嗎
What's wrong, are your training bras too tight?!
塔克教練
Coach Tucker!
請立刻到我辦公室見我
Please see me in my office now!
不 親愛的 我不想去機場
No, honey, I don't want to pick your sister up
接你妹妹
at the airport!
抱歉 我在跟我女朋友說話
Oh, sorry, I'm talking to my girlfriend
碰巧還一直按著喇叭開關
and I accidentally kept the megaphone button pressed!
她最近一直纏著我
She's really been riding me lately,
我跟你們講
let me tell you!
不 親愛的 不
Oh, no sweetheart, no,
我不是故意讓你聽到這些的
I didn't mean for you to hear that!
不 不 你是我的一切 毋庸置疑
No, no, no, you're my everything! Of course!
我給我和米奇爾搞到了
I got tickets for me and Mitchell
在棕櫚泉觀看
to a screening in Palm Springs
《星球大戰之帝國反擊戰》放映會的門票
of "The Empire Strikes Back" --
還有由大明星喬治·盧卡斯
Q&A to follow with the biggest star of all --
主持的問答會
George Lucas.
我特別興奮 因為我有點把米奇
I'm super stoked because I kind of think of Mitch
當成我從未有過的弟弟了
as the brother I never had.
我想不通我們為何不多花點時間待在一起
I don't know why we don't spend more time alone together.
這不是任何人的錯 除了
It's nobody's fault. Except for --
小卡和克萊爾
for Cam and Claire.
你知道嗎 我現在特別高興
You know, I'm as happy now as I've ever been.
看啊 我們在尤凱帕
And look, we're in Yucaipa.
這聽起來像星戰里伊沃克人說的話
That sounds like how Ewoks talk.
我出柜前常溜到尤凱帕的一家同性戀酒吧
I used to sneak off to a gay bar in Yucaipa before I came out.
通常還以為小鎮不會有同性戀酒吧呢
Huh, you don't really think of gay bars as a small-town thing.
有的
Oh, yeah.
不管是鄉村來的同性戀
They serve your rural gays,
沒出柜的同性戀 還是城里來的新手
your closeted gays, your city newbies
都可以去那里適應自己的同性戀生活
looking to get their gay sea-legs,
有點像是去百老匯之前的外地試演
kind of like an out-of-town tryout before they hit Broadway.
看吧 每次和你一起我都能學到新東西
See, I learn something whenever I spend time with you.
還記得你告訴我不要在跳舞時打響指嗎
Remember when you told me not to snap when I dance?
你當時看起來像想弄掉
It looked like you were trying to get peanut butter
手指沾到的花生醬
off your fingers.
說到這個 我餓了
Speaking of which, I'm starving.
其實那家酒吧有很棒的漢堡包
That bar actually has amazing hamburgers
你想停下來吃個午飯嗎
if you want to stop for lunch?
我可以進去嗎
Am I allowed in?
誰會知道呢
Who's gonna know?
別打響指就不會有人知道
Just don't snap.
你覺得我能搞定這件衣服嗎
Do you think I could rock this?
"搞定"這詞沒過時吧
Do people still say rock?
每當你問我年輕人會怎么說的時候
It makes me sad when you have to ask me
我都感覺很難過
what young people say.
艾麗克斯 歌洛莉亞
Alex? Gloria? Ahh!
嗨 嗨
Hmm. Hi. Um, hi!
你在這兒干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
我需要點性感的衣服
I needed some sexy clothes,
所以我就請歌洛莉亞陪我逛街了
so I asked Gloria to help me shop.
無意冒犯我媽
No offense to my mom,
但是她穿得有點保守
but she dresses kind of conservative
而歌洛莉亞知道如何挑選
while Gloria knows how to pick out clothes
能幫我
that will help...
展示一下這寶貝的衣服
take this baby for a spin.
得了 艾麗克斯
Alex, come on,
想那么說起碼自己得相信啊
sell it if you're gonna talk like that.
剛好路過補鞋店
Just stopped by the cobbler
給我的樂福鞋換個鞋底
to get my penny loafers re-soled.
穿了三十年的那雙
Same pair for 30 years.
你們在這兒干什么
What are you guys doing?
我們就是 不 我們
Oh, we're just -- Uh, no, we, uh,
在分別購物 好玩的是
were shopping separately, funniest thing,
我們就突然遇到了對方
and we just bumped into each other!
是吧
Right?
是啊 真是有趣
Yes, it was hilarious.
我在逛街 然后就 就像她說的那樣
I was shopping, and -- and then all she said.
那么你買了什么
So, what did you buy?
不 不 不 這不是我買的
Oh, no, no, no. It's -- It's not mine.
是她的 你能自己拿一會兒嗎
It's hers. Could you hold it for a minute?
我胳膊都酸了
My arms are tired!
她可是示巴女王
This one, the Queen of Sheba.
我們都得服侍著她
We all work for her.
我們玩得很高興
We have fun.
漢堡包很好吃
Burger's amazing.
這地方很不錯
This place is great.
這些小鎮上同性戀們真的厲害
These small town gays have it made.
是啊 雖然他們只能躲在暗處
Yeah, I mean, they're forced to live in the shadows,
但他們能吃到薯條 所以...
but they do get to eat fries, so...
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
那不是格爾·索普嗎
Is that Gil Thorpe?
同性戀們并不全都互相認識 菲爾
We don't all know each other, Phil.
還留著胡子
With the beard.
這里又沒有女人
There are no women in here.
就在那兒 他是我的死敵
Right there, he's my nemesis.
他怎么可能在這里呢
What could he possibly be doing here?
我可能知道哦
I might have a theory.
真不敢相信
Oh, my God!
他在假裝自己是同性戀
He's pretending to be gay.
你在耍什么把戲 格爾
What is your game, Gil?
妮可快來了嗎
is Nicole coming in soon?
她的音浴進行得有點晚
Her sound bath ran late.
有什么特殊活動嗎
Is there a special occasion?
為什么會有特大潛艇堡
Why the party sub?
這是普通大小的潛艇堡啊
this is a normal sandwich.
你好 海莉
Hello, Haley.
這兒怎么有個這么大的潛艇堡
Why the enormous sandwich?
這是很普通的... 算了
This is an ordinary... doesn't matter.
妮可 我們能聊聊嗎
Nicole, can I have a minute?
當然可以
Of course.
你看 現在出了點狀況
Look, a situation has come up
讓我很困惑
and it's pretty confusing.
我還在努力理順情況 但是我...
I'm still trying to process it, but I --
-懷上了 -什么
- Preggo? - What?!
天啊 我就知道
Oh, God, I knew it!
什么
What?!
我是說"淮尚樂" 隨便你怎么念那個
I mean, Prego, you know, however you pronounce
裝逼的意大利時尚網站
that pretentious Italian fashion website.
有人告訴我他們正試著挖走
Someone told me that they're trying
我的一個員工 我不會允許這種事發生
to poach one of my employees, and I am not having it.
說說你想要什么吧
So, what do you need?
我 我...
I, uh, well...
我給你長職位 漲工資 你要升職了
Title bump, money bump -- you are getting a promotion.
你會成為
You are gonna be
新的運動服飾與時代精神的負責人
the new Head of Activewear and Zeitgeist.
我的天 這是我夢想中的工作
Oh, my God, this is my dream job.
我曾跟輔導員說我想做這份工作
I told my guidance counselor that I wanted to do this
她當面笑話了我
and she laughed in my face.
好了 大伙
All right, everyone.
都進來 我們要慶祝
Come in, we're celebrating!
拿把刀來 好讓我們把這個切成二十份
And bring a knife so we can cut this into 20 pieces!
塔克教練 學生們是"受保護群體"
Coach Tucker, students are a "protected class"
你這樣一個有特權的精英白人
and it is not okay for you,
不可以欺負他們
an elite white man of privilege, to bully them.
特權 我只拿教師的薪水
Privilege? I-I make a teacher's salary.
我還是同性戀
And I'm gay.
如今同性戀的標簽不像過去那么好用了
Yeah, gay doesn't really get you the mileage that it used to.
假如你是跨性別者我們就什么問題都沒了
Now, if you were trans, we'd be golden.
全世界都瘋了嗎
Oh, has the whole world gone crazy?!
-杰 -不 我受夠了
- Jay -- - No, no, I've had it.
怎么 所有人都如此敏感
I mean, what, everyone's so sensitive,
他們要把橄欖球也毀了
they're gonna ruin football?
我當年那個球隊
In my day, our team,
漢密爾頓啃白菜佬
the Hamilton Cabbage Eaters,
隊長是猶太佬布龍斯坦
captained by Knish Bronstein,
對抗林肯墨西哥大盜
took on the Lincoln Banditos,
四分衛是"飛鼠"何塞·岡薩雷斯
QB'd by Jose "Speedy" Gonzales.
我們在人堆最底下互捶對方私處
And after three hours of pummeling each other's privates
整整三小時
at the bottom of dog piles,
然后我們像兄弟般握手
we shook hands like brothers
一起去波蘭餃子城吃細香腸
and all went to brawl the Sausage-Heads in Pierogi-Town.
美國
America.
美麗的大熔爐
Beautiful melting pot.
你的生活怎么會是這樣
How was that your life?
你上高中時正好經歷67年愛之夏
You were in high school during the Summer of Love.
塔克教練 我不知道這個人為什么在這
Coach Tucker, I don't know why this man is here,
但他是"老年受保護群體"的一員
but he's a member of the "Elderly protected class,"
法律上來講我們不能反駁他
and legally we can't contradict him.
抱歉 你必須找到更溫和的方法
I'm sorry, you're gonna have to find a gentler way
去激勵你的球員
to motivate your players.
我只知道這一種教練方法
I don't know any other way to coach.
我們需要的是某個玩過橄欖球
What we need is advice from someone who played football
但又很矯情的千禧怪胎給我們建議
but also is a namby-pamby Millennial weirdo.
感謝各位前來
Thank you for coming.
我們今天來這教導這兩位先生
We're here to teach these gentlemen
如何在21世紀與人溝通
how to communicate in the 21st century.
我們先輪流聲明一下自己喜歡的性別代詞
Let's go around and each say the gender pronoun we prefer.
我先開始
I'll start --
我是順性別者 他 他的
I'm cisgender, he-slash-him.
她 她的
She-slash-her.
他們 他們的
They-slash-them.
我不是來為難你們的 叫我鮑勃就行
Oh, I'm not here to bust chops, Bob is fine.
這就是你的橄欖球隊
This is your rugby team?
我被你們這個商場小故事迷住了
I am fascinated by this mall story of yours...
你說你是來購物的
So, you say you were shopping?
是的 你知道我有多愛買鞋
Yes. you know me and shoes.
那我們為什么不把鞋拿出來看看
Well, let's take a look, why don't we?
我都不知道你的腳這么小
I had no idea your foot was so tiny.
是啊 我上面很大下面很小
Yes, I am so big in the top and small in the bottom,
就像南美洲一樣
like South America herself.
-穿上 -真的嗎
- Put 'em on. - Really?
我想看你穿上腳的樣子
I want to see them on your feet.
遵命 女士
Yes, miss.
我感覺我像灰姑娘一樣
I feel like I am Cinderella.
快 美美走兩步給我們看看
Go on, let's see you strut your stuff.
鞋子真漂亮
Pretty shoes.
我從未感覺如此美麗
I've never felt more beautiful!
好了 我看不下去了
Okay, I can't watch this anymore!
媽 拜托別往心里去
Mom, please don't take this personally,
但我今天來和歌洛莉亞購物
but I was shopping with Gloria today
因為我想買些性感的衣服
because I wanted to find something sexy
跟比爾度周末時穿
for my weekend away with Bill,
她比較擅長性感
and that's more her thing.
好吧 我明白
I get it, fine.
我不總穿得像方向盤套一樣
I don't always dress like a...steering wheel cover.
你在發脾氣 我理解
You're lashing out. I understand.
那不意味著我在必要時不能性感起來
Doesn't mean I can't turn it on when I need to.
不只是那點
It's not just that.
我想 我總是覺得
I guess... I don't really feel like
我的情欲讓你很不舒服
you're comfortable with my sexuality.
你和海莉就能談論男人和性
You and Haley can talk about guys and sex,
可你仍把我當12歲小孩看
but you still see me as a 12-year-old.
寶貝 我很抱歉
Honey, I'm sorry.
如果我讓你有那種感覺 我很抱歉
I'm so sorry if I gave you that impression,
但公平點講
but to be fair,
你也不和我分享生活中的那個部分
you don't really share that part of your life with me.
這話也算有理有據
I guess that's valid.
那你要不要給我個機會
So, are you gonna give me a shot?
讓我幫你為比爾裝扮起來
Let me tart you up for Bill.
好 但這不只是為了比爾
Okay. But it is not just for Bill
因為這也是為了我 因為
because it's also for me because I'm --
我要重新展現這部分的自我...
I'm reclaiming a part of myself that I don't think I've really --
沒完沒了說這些玩意
There's a lot of this.
太瘋狂了 他先是離婚 又來這里
This is nuts. First he gets divorced, and now this?
兩件事或許有聯系
Hmm, they may be related.
他還在這嗎
Is he still here?
老天 我被發現了
Oh, man. I've been made!
他在做什么
What's he doing?
他就在你身后
he's right behind you.
鄧菲
Dunphy?
格爾
Hey, Gil.
我在去兔子牧場[妓院]路上停車休息一下
I was just making a pitstop on the way to the Bunny Ranch.
我意外走進這里
I accidentally walked in here
因為一些當地人說這里雞翅很好吃
'cause some local said they had great wings.
我沒意識到一個帶"雞胸"的都沒有
Didn't realize there were no breasts!
我說得對吧
Am I right?!
你不必演了 我叫米奇
You don't have to do this. I'm-I'm Mitch,
我是菲爾的小舅子
I'm Phil's brother-in-law,
你是同性戀也沒關系
and it's okay that you're gay.
什么 等一下 這是瘋話
What? Hold on a second now. that's crazy!
你才是同性戀
You're gay!
是 我知道
Yes, I know.
你以為這是侮辱 但并不是
It's not the insult you think it is.
還是那么有魅力 快走吧 祝你好運
Charming as ever. Off you go. Best of luck.
交給我 好嗎
I got this, okay?
他需要時間來接受真實的自己
It's gonna take him some time to-to accept who he really is.
我是徹頭徹尾的同性戀
I'm totally gay.
你這個開頭很不錯
Wow, you're off to a strong start.
我只是覺得這樣大聲說出來很奇怪
It's just -- it's strange to say it out loud like that,
你懂嗎 我是同性戀
you know? I'm a gay man.
我是個大基佬
I'm a big gay man.
我感覺一個基佬重擔從肩上撤下去了
Feels like a big gay weight has been lifted off me.
光說重擔就行
Just a weight. Yeah.
但終于勇敢面對真實的自己感覺不好嗎
But doesn't it feel great to-to finally own who you really are?
的確感覺很好
Yeah, it does.
我還記得向我爸承認
I remember admitting to my dad
我喜歡魔術
I was into magic.
那可不一樣 鄧菲
It's not the same, Dunphy.
不一樣
It's just not --
老天爺 不過我有好多問題想問你
God, I have so many questions for you, though.
我第一次走進這間酒吧時也一樣
Hey, hey, first time I walked into this bar, I did, too.
盡管問
Fire away.
好
Okay.
只不過在這個繁殖者面前
I'm just not comfortable opening up
我不能自在地敞開心扉
in front of the breeder here, okay?
你生的孩子比我還多
You have more kids than I do!
你這是恐同 伙計
That's homophobic, man!
菲爾 不如你去幫我們拿點喝的吧
Hey, Phil, why don't-why don't you grab us some drinks?
好吧 好吧
Okay. Fine.
來吧
Yeah.
-今天我真走運 -多謝夸獎
- It's my lucky day. - Thank you for that.
但我恐怕已經有主了
But I'm afraid I'm taken.
太遺憾了
That's too bad.
我想遇到個人怎么就這么難
Why is it so hard for me to meet someone?
我
I, um...
我認識個人和你正合適
I have the perfect guy for you.
他很有幽默感 心胸寬大
He has got a great sense of humor, big heart.
我特別喜歡紅頭發
I have a thing for red heads.
他是跟我一起的 是另外那個
He's with me. Uh, the other one.
他 算了吧
Him? Pass.
他都在這游蕩好幾周了
He's been lurking around here for weeks.
我才不在乎
Like I'm impressed he's
他是"南加州第一房地產經紀人"
"Southern California's number one Realtor."
他才不是第一
No, he's not!
你怕什么
Well, what are you afraid of?
我說不好 米奇爾
I don't know, Mitchell.
我這么晚才出柜
I'm so late to the game.
還有誰會想要我
Who's even gonna want me?
米奇爾 時間不早了
Mitchell, um, it's getting late,
我們可不想讓盧卡斯先生苦等
and we don't want to keep Mr. Lucas waiting.
你要走啦
You're leaving?
可是
But...
我在你之前沒和任何人談過這些
You're the first person I ever talked to about any of this stuff.
等一下
One-one second.
菲爾
Phil.
我不能這樣丟下他
I can't leave him this way.
什么 他是個怪物
What?! He's a monster!
還不是工業光魔
And not one of the cool ones
創造出的那些很酷的怪物
created by Industrial Light and Magic!
我知道 這件事很難接受
I know. This-this is a lot to take in,
但我認為他內心是個很好的人
but I think that there's a really good guy in there
他需要我
and-and he needs me.
抱歉 你走吧 玩得開心點
I'm sorry, you go, have fun.
你選他不選我
You're-you're picking him over me?!
不 我只是需要確保他沒事
No. I just need to make sure he's okay.
我會試著趕過去的
Look, I-I'll try and get there if I can.
要么做要么不做
Do, or do not.
沒有所謂的試著
There is no try.
求你別引用尤達訓我
Please don't Yoda me.
二十年前 我在這間酒吧里
Twenty years ago, I was in this bar,
和你有一樣的感覺
feeling just like you do.
有個很友善的人來和我聊天
And this really nice guy came up to talk to me.
我想他看出了我有多迷失多孤獨
I-I think he could see how lost and alone I was.
我說不好
And, I don't know,
我感覺我的整個世界都在那天敞開了
it felt like my whole world opened up that day.
這個故事讓人很有感觸
Wow, that's a touching story.
我們什么時候開始"感觸"一下彼此
So when are we gonna start touching?
不好意思 什么
I'm sorry, what?
要我說我們去停車場
I say we head out to the parking lot,
在我前妻的小型貨車里瘋狂一把吧
get a little crazy in my ex-wife's minivan, huh?
不 不要 真惡心
No! No, gross!
行吧 哈里王子
Fine, Prince Harry.
我花錢開個房就是了
I'll pop for a hotel room.
但花錢我就全套都要"做"到
But that means we're doing everything.
夠了 你真是爛人
Okay. Y-You're awful!
好歹我不會勾引人又不給上啊
Well, at least I'm not a tease.
我一下午都讓你給浪費掉了
What a waste of an afternoon.
我叫格爾 剛剛出柜
Hey, I'm Gil. Just came out.
感到有點迷失與孤單
Feeling kind of lost and alone.
你們快跑
You, run.
有人能載我一程嗎
C-C-Can someone give me a ride?
我需要去追帶我來的那個男人
I need to go after the guy I was here with.
走吧 那男人值得去追
Let's go. He's worth it.
安全帽
Ooh, a hat.
有意思
Fun.
我不確定這件好不好
I don't know about this.
出來吧 親愛的 我選的
Come on, honey, I picked it out.
我絕對不會嫌棄你 我發誓
I'm not gonna judge you. I swear.
你看起來真美
You look beautiful.
我愛死了
I love it.
你確定嗎 不會太露嗎
Really? It's not too much?
假正經的人才會喜歡若隱若現
Let the prudes leave something to the imagination.
比爾肯定會"快讓我來品品這美女"
Bill's gonna be all, "Let me get a piece of that," huh?
再幫你挑內衣如何
How about lingerie?
我肯定會喜歡你幫我挑選的內衣
Yes, um, I would love your input on my lingerie.
比爾會喜歡什么款
What would Bill like?
用扣子的款式
Something with snaps.
他不太喜歡解太復雜的服飾
He doesn't like complicated garments.
他很容易失去耐心
He's easily frustrated.
知道這一點真是太有趣了
That is so fun to know.
我能說我對你的情欲感到自在嗎
Can I just say, I am so comfortable with your sexuality.
我也想說你對我的情欲感到自在
Can I just say that your comfort with my sexuality
也令我對自己的情欲感到自在
has made me more comfortable with my sexuality.
我能說如果我包里帶了我的槍
Can I just say that if I had my gun in my purse,
我一定會開槍爆自己頭嗎
I would shoot myself.
菲爾
Phil!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我真的很對不起
I am so sorry!
你的確該感到抱歉
Well, you should be!
菲爾
Phil!
聽他解釋嘛 他很過意不去
Hear him out, he feels terrible!
你真的沒說錯格爾 他就是個爛人
You were right about Gil! He's awful!
他這人簡直無藥可救了
He has no redeeming qualities,
只有挑男人的眼光還過得去
well, except for his taste in men!
你知道這事對我來說有多重要嗎
You know how important this was to me?!
當然啦
Of course!
我也是跟你一樣瘋狂的《星球大戰》腦殘粉
I-I'm as big a "Star Wars" Fan as you are!
其實完全跟《星球大戰》無關
It was never about "Star Wars"!
這一切都只是為了跟你共處
It was about spending time with you!
真的嗎
Oh, really?!
是啊
Yes!
我也愛跟你一起玩啊
Well, I love spending time with you!
真的嗎
You do?!
當然啊
Totally!
你就像是我未曾有過的哥哥
You're like the brother I never had!
真的嗎 這話也太不可思議了吧
What?! That's crazy cakes!
-我也整天說你像我弟 -少來啦
- I say that about you all the time! - Stop it!
我完全誤會了你們之間的關系
I had a totally different idea about what this was,
但這還是好感人
but it's still beautiful!
注意看路 注意看路
Eyes on the road! Eyes on the road!
怎么啦
Hey, what's going on?
今天經歷太多事了
Today's been a lot.
我也是
Same.
這話我感覺我不常說
You know, I don't say it enough,
但我很慶幸我們倆能無話不談
but I am so glad that you and I can talk about anything.
跟艾麗克斯發生什么了嗎
Something happen with Alex?
我不想談
I don't want to talk about it.
那又是何事讓你坐到這里了
What brings you to the floor?
這個嘛...
Well...
我好像讓自己....
it seems I've gone and gotten myself...
升職了
...promoted.
海莉 那很棒啊
Haley, that's fantastic!
是啊
Yeah.
是啊 以后我會有個人停車位與"個休"
Yeah, I, uh -- I get my own parking spot and an "IRA."
我猜是我新助手的名字之類的
I guess that's my assistant's name or something?
親愛的 我很以你為榮
Sweetheart, I'm very proud of you.
你真的扭轉了自己的生活
You really pulled it together.
或許吧 但我還是有好多東西得弄明白
Yeah, well, I still have a lot of stuff to figure out.
當然啦
Of course you do.
每個人在你這年齡都這樣
Everyone does at your age.
媽呀 我當年就這樣
Boy, I know I did.
你發現懷了我時 有后悔過嗎
Did you ever regret having me when you did?
感覺讓你的事業脫離了正軌
Like how it kinda derailed your career?
我一開始的確不太開心
I didn't love it at first.
直到我看到了這張臉
But then I saw this face.
而且你很幸運能有爸這樣的好男人陪你
And you were lucky enough to have Dad.
他天生就是個當爸爸的料
He was born to be a parent.
這話或許會讓你感到驚訝
This is gonna come as a surprise to you,
但當年你爸并不是你想的這個人
but your dad was a different guy than you think.
什么 那是哪個人 所以我才這么矮嗎
What?! Who?! Is that why I'm so short?!
不是啦 海莉
No! Haley!
當我認識你爸爸的時候
When I met your father,
他的生活還是一團亂
he did not have his life together.
但不得不夸他
But to his credit,
他真的在我懷孕后扛起了責任
he really stepped up when I got pregnant,
所以才能順利懷著孩子吧
and I think that's what made it work.
因為有一個能依靠的人
You know, having someone to depend on.
我怎么會聊到這個事情
How did I get down this road?
我不知道啊
I don't know!
再見啦
Bye!
再見
Okay.
為什么艾麗克斯穿得像暴露狂出去了
Why is Alex leaving the house dressed like a flasher?
我們說好不談這事了
She and I agreed not to discuss it.
她情欲崛起這事我們大家都不好受
Her sexual awakening has been tough on all of us.
是啊
Yes.
湯普森 我看到你也聽得到你 我在聆聽你
Thompson, I see you, I hear you, and I'm listening!
我很希望你能按照我們說好的戰術打
I would have preferred you stuck to the play we called,
但我尊重你的獨立意志
but I respect your independent spirit!
好 平托斯基 把四分衛周圍區域
Okay, Pitkowski, treat the area around the quarterback
當成是"安全空間"
as a "safe space,"
把對方的防守球員們
and think of the other team's defenders
當成是要來破壞你自尊的惡念
as destructive thoughts trying to attack our self-esteem!
行不通
It's not working.
我真不想輸給吉祥物是維京人的隊伍
I hate losing to a team with a Viking mascot.
你們滅了然后變成瑞典人
You died out and became Swedes!
為你們的社會主義與季節性抑郁癥歡呼
Hip-hip-hooray for socialism and seasonal depression!
這事關我們的冠軍獎杯
Our championship is on the line.
你得做點什么啊
You gotta do something.
這是你們人生中最重大的時刻
Men, this is the biggest moment of your life
但我不知道怎么才能鼓舞你們
and I don't know how to fire you up!
我原來的計劃是來這里比賽后
My original plan was to come in here,
挑出表現不好的人
single out the under-performers
然后往他們身上扔紙尿布
and throw diapers at them!
現在我意識到會有人覺得我不照顧他人感受
Now I realize that could be interpreted as insensitive
甚至可能是反嬰兒
or, perhaps, anti-baby!
對不起
I'm sorry,
但球場一直都是我的安全空間
but the football field was always my safe space, okay?!
高中時在球場上
It's where, in high school,
我第一次得到了同輩的尊敬
I first gained the respect of my peers,
如果讓我老實說
and if I'm being honest,
我也希望能在球場上
where I'd hoped I'd finally gain
終于得到我丈人的贊賞
the admiration of my father-in-law.
但現在我只感覺到
Now I feel like I've just...
我辜負了你們
let you all down.
你們想知道我的感想嗎
You want to know how I feel?
為塔克教練不知道
Hurt that Coach Tucker doesn't know
我們多感激他而感到難過
how much we appreciate him.
我也不滿他做了這么多來向我們證明
Triggered because he's got to apologize
自己是個爺們與好教練
for a few words after all he's done
卻得因為說錯幾句話而道歉
to prove himself as a man and a coach.
我其實欣賞你很久了
I've admired you for a long time
但我一直都沒讓你知道 這是我的錯
and if I haven't let you know that, that's on me --
而我都能像個"陰柔人"一樣承認了
and I'm "Cissy-gendered" enough to admit it.
從今往后
And from now on,
我會確保塔克教練知道
I'm gonna make sure that Coach Tucker knows
他是受我欽佩與尊敬的人
he's a person of value I admire and respect.
塔克教練是受我欽佩與尊敬的人
Coach Tucker's a person of value I admire and respect!
現在去打敗你們的對手
Now let's go take it to these guys,
我很肯定他們肯定有別的才華
who I'm sure are blessed with other gifts
但橄欖球方面一定不行
but are not great at football!
沖啊
Let's go!
你敢相信他們居然買賬嗎
Can you believe they bought it?
買什么
Bought what?
我們生活在敏感的年代
We live in sensitive times.
沒有嗎
Nothing?
完全沒腦子嗎
No brain at all?
這肯定要影響到我事業了
Well, that's gonna hurt my career.
所以如果我們想成功 就得與時俱進
So we must evolve if we want to succeed.
有時候這需要我們分享自己的脆弱
Sometimes that requires us to share our vulnerabilities...
才能用嶄新的視角看待彼此
...so that we can see one another in a new way.
你還好嗎
How are you doing?
我想我同意這事
I think I'm okay with it.
我很害怕
I'm scared.
但知道會有你陪我讓我感到不那么害怕了
But it's less scary knowing I'm going through it with you.
今天的無宗教性
That concludes today's non-denominational
鼓舞宣言就到此結束啦
inspirational affirmation.
祝你有順你意的一天
Have the day that's right for you.
看看你們這群小王八蛋還有什么能抱怨
Let's see those little bastards complain about that.
慘了
Oh, no!
沒錯 抬高膝蓋
That's right guys. High knees.
抬高膝蓋
High knees.
左方有蘇聯共匪
Commie to your left.
右方有蘇聯共匪
Commie to your right.
腳別拖泥帶水啊 平托斯基
Stop dragging Pitkowski.
他們要來搶走你的心上人啦
They are coming after your sweet heart.
你知道他們怎么摧殘了波蘭嗎
You know what they did to Poland?
我很想叫停這一切
Well, I wanna stop this.
但執導手冊里完全沒寫到有關共黨的東西
But there is nothing in the guidelines about communists.
我們像個嬉皮士這么嗨高高[吸大麻]
Now we are high like a hippie.
-彎下腰像個基... -好了 杰 停下
- We are bending over like a ga... - Ok, shut it down Jay.
好啦 各位 用我教的方法喝水
Alright, boys. Hydrate like I tought you.
很乖
Attaboy.
這就對了
There you go.